[{"answer": "With $1.6 trillion in new taxes, I think probably half a second.", "docId": "121129pmt", "aSentId": 36, "question": "How many seconds was it, do you think, gentlemen -- let me start with you, if I may, Frank -- before John Boehner rejected out of hand President Obama's attempt to try and do a fiscal cliff deal?", "qSentId": 35}, {"answer": "Well, I mean, they care in largest part about staying in office, and one of the problems here is what each individual member of Congress thinks he or she needs to do to stay in office is not necessarily in concert with someone else -- with what someone else thinks.", "docId": "121129pmt", "aSentId": 49, "question": "What do you think, Frank?", "qSentId": 48}, {"answer": "Ross Douthat, I mean, from where I sit, having interviewed all the protagonists now for the last week as we head to this incredibly dull 30 days of the same debate being played out -- eventually, we know they'll do a deal.", "docId": "121129pmt", "aSentId": 53, "question": "And I think it's hard for everyone to pull back, look at things from a macro level and say, What's best for the country because each person is saying, What's best for me?", "qSentId": 52}, {"answer": "I sort of do think they will because in certain ways, from the Republican perspective, you could argue that the smartest thing to do is to, you know, vote -- vote to extend all the Bush tax cuts, let President Obama veto that extension, then vote a middle class tax cut and let the top bracket expire.", "docId": "121129pmt", "aSentId": 88, "question": "Do you think they're going to end in the end have to acquiesce to that?", "qSentId": 87}, {"answer": "Well, it's interesting.", "docId": "121129pmt", "aSentId": 109, "question": "And in the end, isn't that what everybody would like to see at the end of this very complicated, rather dangerous rainbow?", "qSentId": 108}, {"answer": "Well, you know, it would be great to have a celebration.", "docId": "121129pmt", "aSentId": 127, "question": "Well, why can't they just be grown-up about this, accept that there's movement on both sides to be done, and get it done over a turkey at the White House?", "qSentId": 126}, {"answer": "It's about statehood.", "docId": "121129pmt", "aSentId": 151, "question": "Why does it mean so much to Palestinians that the U.N. today has slightly upgraded your status?", "qSentId": 150}, {"answer": "Absolutely.", "docId": "121129pmt", "aSentId": 191, "question": "Do you believe that is in reality what could happen here?", "qSentId": 190}, {"answer": "Piers, you know, I was there at the United Nations, as you know, and I listened carefully because I thought, you know, today, we will hear a speech by a leader like Sadat who would go to the end of the earth to achieve peace.", "docId": "121129pmt", "aSentId": 214, "question": "What is your response?", "qSentId": 213}, {"answer": "Look, as you know, I was -- and I think Dr. Erakat was with me on the negotiation table.", "docId": "121129pmt", "aSentId": 228, "question": "Do you think a deal can actually get done, or are we just basically just going to see a lot more posturing before more missiles start ricocheting around on both sides?", "qSentId": 227}, {"answer": "First of all, thank you for asking me because I heard you talk about it once, and being Israel's ambassador, former ambassador to the court of St. James, you would agree with me that even the craziest of crazy, Northern Ireland, did not claim London as the capital.", "docId": "121129pmt", "aSentId": 246, "question": "Are you guys prepared to sit down with Hamas leaders and actually deal directly with people who many believe now have more authority than the Palestinian authority?", "qSentId": 245}, {"answer": "I'm doing great.", "docId": "121129pmt", "aSentId": 292, "question": "Mike, how are you?", "qSentId": 291}, {"answer": "Absolutely.", "docId": "121129pmt", "aSentId": 301, "question": "You think he's done a good enough job to deserve being re-elected?", "qSentId": 300}, {"answer": "We have to have some Republican representative and he has to tell you.", "docId": "121129pmt", "aSentId": 307, "question": "Why are the Republicans so out of touch?", "qSentId": 306}, {"answer": "Health care.", "docId": "121129pmt", "aSentId": 314, "question": "When you go back to your old streets and you meet your old guys and so on, what do you think the real cares and fears of the average American on the street are right now?", "qSentId": 313}, {"answer": "Real -- from my perspective, I can only tell you -- as you're asking me, from my ordeals in life and challenges.", "docId": "121129pmt", "aSentId": 326, "question": "Where is real happiness throughout that process?", "qSentId": 325}, {"answer": "You know, I wanted Lindsey to win so bad.", "docId": "121129pmt", "aSentId": 357, "question": "What advice could you give somebody like that?", "qSentId": 356}, {"answer": "She needs a good support system.", "docId": "121129pmt", "aSentId": 364, "question": "What does she need to do, Mike, to get out of it?", "qSentId": 363}, {"answer": "I've met her, yes.", "docId": "121129pmt", "aSentId": 370, "question": "Have you met her before?", "qSentId": 369}, {"answer": "I think she's an awesome person that's just got to get it together.", "docId": "121129pmt", "aSentId": 372, "question": "What do you think of her?", "qSentId": 371}, {"answer": "No, he's real good.", "docId": "121129pmt", "aSentId": 399, "question": "He's not bad, is he?", "qSentId": 398}, {"answer": "Yeah, I really did.", "docId": "121129pmt", "aSentId": 409, "question": "Did you enjoy that?", "qSentId": 408}, {"answer": "YSON: He's an awesome little kid.", "docId": "121129pmt", "aSentId": 412, "question": "What was he like?", "qSentId": 411}, {"answer": "He's average size.", "docId": "121129pmt", "aSentId": 414, "question": "He's really tiny, isn't he?", "qSentId": 413}, {"answer": "His mother likes birds.", "docId": "121129pmt", "aSentId": 417, "question": "What did you talk about?", "qSentId": 416}, {"answer": "Yeah.", "docId": "121129pmt", "aSentId": 420, "question": "You talked about pigeons?", "qSentId": 419}, {"answer": "No, but I believe his mother had birds.", "docId": "121129pmt", "aSentId": 422, "question": "Does he keep pigeons?", "qSentId": 421}, {"answer": "I have at least a hundred at my house now, yes.", "docId": "121129pmt", "aSentId": 425, "question": "Do you still keep pigeons?", "qSentId": 424}, {"answer": "Yes, that's what I do.", "docId": "121129pmt", "aSentId": 427, "question": "You love them, don't you?", "qSentId": 426}, {"answer": "I can' tell you.", "docId": "121129pmt", "aSentId": 429, "question": "What is it about the pigeon?", "qSentId": 428}, {"answer": "I feel like I'm in heaven.", "docId": "121129pmt", "aSentId": 432, "question": "When you're with them, what do you feel?", "qSentId": 431}, {"answer": "Always.", "docId": "121129pmt", "aSentId": 439, "question": "You have always been like that with them?", "qSentId": 438}, {"answer": "Watch the left hook.", "docId": "121129pmt", "aSentId": 465, "question": "Freddy?", "qSentId": 464}, {"answer": "I think that it was really horrible.", "docId": "121129pmt", "aSentId": 497, "question": "What did you think of my left hook technically, though?", "qSentId": 496}, {"answer": "Yeah, I knew Hector.", "docId": "121129pmt", "aSentId": 506, "question": "Did you know Hector?", "qSentId": 505}, {"answer": "Yeah, then you go to drugs, too.", "docId": "121129pmt", "aSentId": 516, "question": "How hard is it, Mike, for people who have been at the top of boxing, with all the adrenaline, the buildup to these fights for months; then you get in there, the adrenaline rush, the public going crazy, and then the actual fight; and then suddenly it's all over; you don't have it in your life anymore?", "qSentId": 515}, {"answer": "Well, I don't put myself in those situations.", "docId": "121129pmt", "aSentId": 525, "question": "How do you feel now?", "qSentId": 524}, {"answer": "I don't know.", "docId": "121129pmt", "aSentId": 538, "question": "When was the last time you hit a man?", "qSentId": 537}, {"answer": "The photographer, yeah.", "docId": "121129pmt", "aSentId": 541, "question": "Remember that ordeal?", "qSentId": 540}, {"answer": "Yeah.", "docId": "121129pmt", "aSentId": 543, "question": "Good shot?", "qSentId": 542}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "121129pmt", "aSentId": 563, "question": "Really?", "qSentId": 562}, {"answer": "I want you in that film.", "docId": "121129pmt", "aSentId": 569, "question": "Can you beat on a monkey or something?", "qSentId": 568}, {"answer": "I don't know.", "docId": "121129pmt", "aSentId": 602, "question": "When you hear him talk about what you did to him and for his life, what do you think?", "qSentId": 601}, {"answer": "Listen, I don't know if someone needs someone like Cus.", "docId": "121129pmt", "aSentId": 611, "question": "Does everybody need somebody like a Cus D'Amato to just get a grip of them?", "qSentId": 610}, {"answer": "We're going to go all over, 36 cities across the nation.", "docId": "121129pmt", "aSentId": 623, "question": "What are you going to do with it next?", "qSentId": 622}, {"answer": "The city I did my time in and stuff.", "docId": "121129pmt", "aSentId": 628, "question": "Really?", "qSentId": 627}, {"answer": "That's going to be pretty awesome.", "docId": "121129pmt", "aSentId": 630, "question": "How will that feel?", "qSentId": 629}, {"answer": "Knocking out is not necessarily having a hard punch.", "docId": "121129pmt", "aSentId": 651, "question": "If I was to really want to knock somebody out, what is the absolutely best way to do it?", "qSentId": 650}]